question.
>> What's the last 24? Well, really, uh, 12
hours been like for you,
>> man. It's been fantastic. It's not
>> on
everyone. I'm getting mic. You get mic.
Everyone else get mic.
>> I got it.
>> Good.
>> All right, we'll go.
>> Yeah, sorry about that.
>> Okay. Yeah. No, the the last uh couple,
you know, 12 hours has been it's been
surreal, man. You know, hearing my name
called uh I was feeling emotions I never
felt before, man. Overflowing joy. So,
uh, it's been great, you know, hanging
out with my, you know, agency, uh, Texas
Tech staff and, you know, my friends,
family, and everything. So, it's been
great.
>> How many text messages have you gotten
the last throughout that time?
>> I've got a lot, man. I didn't I I don't
have my notifications on, so I got asked
that yesterday, but I had a good amount.
I'm still replying to a lot of them.
>> You said yesterday limited
interaction with her life, but now that
you've been here and everything like
that, what have the conversations been
like?
>> Uh, I I haven't met with them. Yeah, I
haven't met with them today. Yeah, I
mean I've seen him for I seen him uh a
little bit in the wait room just to
introduce myself, but I haven't had like
a formal meeting with him yet.
>> One of the things um I said last night,
David, about the three of you guys is
that you all came from winning programs,
right? You guys were all in the playoffs
last year. I know you weren't at tech
long, but you guys kind of turned things
around there last year. Do you feel like
you learned something there that you can
bring here because this team is trying
to to turn it around?
>> Yeah, 100%, man. I mean, uh, you know,
the reason that we had the success we
had at Tech was, you know, a lot lot
more than me, man. It just a whole bunch
of things. It was, you know, Maguire and
it was the staff and it was the alumni
and the, you know, players that we
acquired acquired. So, um, you know, I I
but I learned for myself like at least
uh what's important for success is, you
know, creating a great routine, you
know, effective routine and staying
consistent to that routine. So, I'm
looking to carry um carry on the same
thing uh in my pro career. um you know
just creating a even better routine uh
to to help me become a better player. So
>> did you get to meet Frank Reich when he
was coming in through that transition
and you were leaving Stanford? Was there
any
>> Yeah, yeah, I met Reich. Um, so at prior
to my pro day, uh, the Jets, I had a
dinner with them and Reich was actually
there and I was sitting there and I was
looking at him a little funny and I was
like, you know, you look famili familiar
and then he was like, yeah, like I was I
was coaching at Stanford uh with with
Luck. Um, and you know, he talked to me,
we talked about a couple players like
Sam Rous and everything and chopped it
up. Um, but you know, we both had we
said the same thing about Stanford. It's
a great great uh great spot with great
players and um, you know, this is
amazing campus and great university as a
whole. So
>> David, did you get to know uh Arll at
all throughout this process or did you
have a history with him? You know, you
you guys were sort of wanted to two one
on a lot of people's boards with the
position and both in New York.
>> Yeah. No. Um my my uh communication or
contact with him was like limited. Uh
you know, say what's up. Um you know,
good luck and what what not, but yeah,
it was limited.
>> I'm sorry. I was going to say you guys
are sort of listed as the same position,
but you play you play different
positions. Is that how you would
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. I would say that. Yeah.
>> After your three years at Stanford,
did you reach out to the league?
Sometimes there's that advisory board on
where you might go in the draft if
you're thinking of coming out. As far as
where did you think you were going to go
if you did come out compared to going
second overall? Obviously, things worked
out so well for you. Yeah, I I bro I I
honestly didn't think at all of leaving
after Stanford. I mean, I had one more
year. Um and I had put, you know, I had
graded pretty high on my PFF, but you
know, I didn't put anything on tape that
I was like extremely proud of. So, I
didn't really think of leaving after
three years, but um I want to say like
fourth round. I really don't know to be
honest. Um I know a couple of my my
teammates were asking why I didn't
leave, but you know, I just felt like I
need another year.
>> What did you feel like you improved on
during that year? Yeah, I mean I feel
like I improved on uh my understanding
of the game, you know, as a whole, my
football IQ. Um and then obviously my
pass rushing ability too, you know,
getting under coach AU was was great
because, you know, he's super
knowledgeable about pass rushing and he,
you know, he took my game to the next
level and that was like the first time I
could really rely on the on my coach
for, you know, uh pass rushing um
techniques that, you know, I could that
transferred over the game. So, yeah.
Were there head rushers or pass rushers
that you studied or watched, whether it
be pros or college?
>> Yeah, for sure. I watched a lot of um
watched a lot of Von Miller. Um you
know, that was probably the first uh
professional player that I started
watching and you know, I I watched him a
little bit freshman year. Um not really
too intense, like not studying his film,
just a little something. Uh but I think
it was after that sophomore year is when
I started like really honing in on him.
Um you know, I'd watch his, you know,
his his highlights. Uh, I'd create like
cutups on on my phone and you know
whenever I was doing like extra work
over on the weekends and I'll get on the
tire guy and try to like emulate you
know his moves and stuff like that. So I
watch a lot of Vaughn um I know I got my
like pass rush uh stance you know the
three-point stance get off from Aiden
Hutchinson you know uh I thought it was
he has an elite get off. Um, so yeah,
those are the two main ones. And then,
um, shoot, I just go on Instagram, man.
And Instagram's got a lot of like, you
know, Dline page, Dline Guru. I got a
lot of cutups that, you know, I I
sometimes save into a folder. And then
if I see something that I like that I
can, you know, I think I could, you
know, maybe translate to the game, I
I'll do it, save it.
>> When did you know that this was a
possibility that the pros were something
that, you know, you could be not maybe
not a first round draft pick, but a
professional football player?
>> Yeah. Um, I'd probably say
I'd probably say I started really going
after it um my sophomore year um of of
college. Um, you know, I had I didn't
really have a great season. Um, and you
know, I wasn't happy with my success or
you know, the team success. So, um,
that's when I started turning things
around. My approach to the game
completely changed. Um, my attitude
towards, you know, rehab and um, extra
work and film study completely changed.
uh it did a complete 180. So um yeah.
>> Was there anything in particular that
that really helped flip that switch or
like anybody influence you with that?
>> No, really just the disappointment that
I felt like in my in myself and just the
disappointment I felt like in in the
team. Um just kind of like Yeah, that
was probably the main motivating factor.
>> When your brother was your brother
played at Harvard?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Did you come to this part of the country
a lot to watch him play? Most of the Ivy
League schools are in the 80s. Did you
what was that experience like?
>> Yeah. No, I never actually uh saw a game
in person. Um we would watch like the
games. Um we watch like the games online
sometimes. Um but yeah, I never seen uh
saw his game in person. Um but you know,
I came out for his graduation. Um but
yeah.
>> What was his influence on you? Obviously
you you're a good student, too, and he's
obviously a very good student going to
Harvard.
>> Yeah.
>> His influence on you.
>> Oh, his influence on me. Oh. Oh, I mean
just his his approach to to academics,
man. I mean, you know, generally
speaking, like the general notion of
like football players is, you know, they
just don't take academics seriously.
It's kind of all football, but you know,
he was able to balance both football and
in school and be elite at both of them.
So, uh, I felt like I had that same
ability to do so. So,
>> how important was it to, uh, get your
degree from Stanford before, uh, moving
on to Texas Tech and obviously now the
NFL?
>> Yeah, it was extremely important. And
then um you know I was uncertain in how
long it would take to get it. But uh you
know I really I didn't know I was going
to graduate early till after freshman
year. So um you know after freshman year
I got I knew it was a possibility. I
knew I wanted something better for my
football career. Um which which entailed
me transferring. So you know I got my
academic uh shout out TJ Bernett. But
you know he helped me taking like uh
summer classes and extracurriculars and
whatnot um in order to help me graduate.
So, you know, it was extremely important
good getting in there and and finishing
what I started. So,
>> is there is there any quarterback in the
NFL that you're particularly looking
forward with the sacking?
>> Yeah, Bryce Young, if I ever get the
chance.
>> You guys are you still close? I know you
guys.
>> Yeah. Yeah, actually. Um I mean, not
close uh just cuz you know there's like
a little bit of an age uh age gap, but
um you know where I train at right now
uh for my pass rushing back home is at
Golden West College. And I don't know if
y'all know, but like a lot of the
quarterbacks uh train down there. Um you
know, uh Bryce Young and you Noah Fida.
Um so like a lot of elite quarterbacks
over there. So I actually just saw him
probably like two weeks ago. Um he
chopped it up, gave me some advice. You
know what I'm saying? So
>> now that it's water under the bridge,
the whole thing where you didn't come
here for the meeting?
>> Yeah.
>> Were what were your emotions after that?
Did you think maybe they're not going to
pick me or did you kind of know all
along the the meeting thing was
overrated? Um,
initially I probably thought like, yeah,
they're not they're not going to uh pick
me. But then also I was thinking back um
to the interactions that I had with
them, you know, prior to that uh to the
meeting getting cancelled and I was
thinking back uh to the interaction I
had them at the combine and at the
steakhouse and the facetimes with Muji
and I was like, you know, this is I had
a good relationship with them like you
know, I felt I felt good talking to
them. I felt like they had a good
attitude towards me and vice versa. So,
um, so yeah, no, I I really after that,
uh, after they canceled it and, you
know, I got with my my agent, he was
like, you know, don't think too much
about it, you know, you know, just trust
the process, trust what they're doing.
Um, and just stay consistent, man. So,
yeah.
>> You faced you faced Oregon in the
playoff. What do you remember about
Sadique?
>> Oh, yeah. I remember. Um, I remember
there's a lot of game planning against
him. I remember
he was probably I think we we we
identified him as the best like
offensive player to be honest. Um
besides quarterback uh but yeah I think
we identified him as like the best
offensive player. Um you know he's
extremely fast. Uh he has a great size
on him for a tight end. Um so yeah
appreciate y
I'm doing good. How are you?
>> Just describe what these last uh 12 16
hours have been like.
>> Uh it's been just a really good uh fun
time. Exciting. It was very anxious at
first, but uh just when I got a call, it
was just very exciting time and just fun
time and a relief of stress.
>> You you said last night when 16 passed,
you didn't think you'd be here?
>> Yes, sir.
>> What was what happened after that for
you? What were you thinking and when did
you actually find out?
>> Uh I actually found out um I mean what I
was thinking I mean just maybe somebody
else is going to possibly get me. Uh,
but I found out once they called me, I
didn't even know they traded back up
until I got the call and uh, Coach Muji,
I mean Darren Muji told me that they
traded up. Uh, and that's kind of when I
figured out
>> why did you want to be here so badly?
>> Uh, I mean just the the city and state
of New York. Um, just a really good
atmosphere, the coaching staff that that
Aaron Glenn has brought out here. uh
just really good people uh that loves
football, love ball, and has a great
game, a great plan. Um and I've just I
wanted to be a part of that.
>> Do you know much about the offensive
personnel here like Gino Smith and
Garrett Wilson and so forth, your new
teammate?
>> Uh yes, sir. I know about a few of them
um and have watched them in the past, of
course. What
>> about Garrett Wilson? I mean, played
obviously by the school as well.
>> Uh yeah, I actually grew up a Ohio State
Buckeyes fan. So, um, I was actually a
fan of him when I was younger.
>> What, um, you touched on this a little
bit last night, but what do you think
you can take from the lesson at IU of
turning things around there, make a
difference here?
>> Uh, I mean, I would just say like the
mindset, the mindset that I, uh, was
instilled into me. Um, and then just
trying to bring others along. Um, and
also just creating a relationship with
trying to with everybody in the locker
room. I feel like that kind of helped us
be successful because we were out there
playing for each other as well. So,
>> you said you're a fan of Garrett and I'm
guessing you know Adai from his time
with the Colts too, right? So, how do
you see yourself fitting in with that
group and what do you think that group
is going to be?
>> Um, I am not sure yet. Um, that's really
for the coaches. Uh, I haven't we
haven't had that conversation yet. Um,
and so I'm looking forward to see what
they say, but I feel like that is a
really good group of receivers. Um, and
we could do something special, but I
mean it ain't going to be given to us.
We got to go out there and prove it and
earn it every single day. So, uh,
that'll be really exciting just to be a
part of that group.
>> What was it you liked about Garrett's
game?
>> Uh, I mean really everything. Uh, just
he was had some really good releases,
really good route runner, and attacked
the ball really good, really well in
college especially. um and just how um
aggressive he played. That was something
that I really uh found found uh
enjoyable.
>> Has it sunk in yet that you teammates?
>> Uh no, not yet.
>> You just posted the video of the call to
you last night and Aaron Glenn was
referencing being in his office,
>> his message.
>> Did you feel like a a bond there or did
you feel like it seemed like he he
referenced a pretty powerful
conversation you guys had? Uh yeah, I
the conversation that we had in his
office uh felt like we just connected
really well and uh just everything that
he was talking about I really I really
enjoyed what I was hearing and really
love what I was hearing and I told him I
mean that's something that I would love
to be a part of and so uh the fact that
he actually came and got me I was
grateful.
>> And then Sean Jefferson seemed pretty
excited.
>> Oh yeah.
>> What have your impressions been of him
so far? Uh, I mean, just everything like
you said, his energy. Uh, he has some
really high energy. Love how he how he's
just uh not aggressive, but I just like
that. Uh, and then he's going he's going
to be hard on you. He's going to tell
you what you need to hear and not what
you want to hear. And I just that's a
that's type of coach that I I want to be
uh coached by. Um, and so I'm looking
forward to it.
>> What's the last few months been like
going from winning the national
championship to the first round? Uh it's
been really busy. Um you go straight
into training from that championship for
combine and pro day and then you go uh
visits. I had a lot of visits. So uh
it's just been very busy, a little
overwhelming, but at the same time it's
been a good time just being able to be a
part of something like that. Uh and it's
a dream come true. So I've been very
grateful for the opportunities I've been
given.
>> How many 30 visits did you do?
>> I did 12.
>> Wow. Yes, sir.
>> Omar, about three hours down the road
here at Penn State, you had that play
that will uh be one of the greatest
plays in college history. How much do
you think that play You had a good
resume anyway. You think that even
enhanced your resume even more with the
pros?
>> Uh, I would say, yeah, I mean that's
kind of I feel like that's kind of what
got my name really known. Um, I feel
like just that play they started really
seeing who I was. Um, and started
watching me a little bit more after
that.
>> You were fan of Garrett, but was there
somebody you patterned some of your
skills after? Like was there somebody
you really watched when you were
younger?
>> Um, when I was really younger, Julio
Jones. Um, but obviously uh definitely
not the same type of player. Uh, but
this past season I wa I liked watching
Jamar Chase, Devonte Adams, and Aman
Ros.
>> Was there anything that was said about
you during the pre-draw process? You
know, you hear all the mock drafts and
the media reports and stuff that you
felt was wrong as a any criticisms of
your game that you felt were off.
>> Uh, I mean, no. I mean, if somebody
feels like that, then I mean, I loved
hearing it cuz I feel like that that
means I still got something to work on
and improve. Um, and so I feel like that
just helps me become a better player and
so I like hearing that type stuff. Um,
cuz it always pushes me to get better.
>> What do you feel like you improved on
the most while you're at Indiana?
>> Uh, I would say just my mentality and
mindset. Um, I feel like that changed
tremendously throughout my career. Um,
and it just allowed me to be more free
when I'm playing.
>> A couple more. Obviously, the talk for
months, it seems like it's been forever,
that Fernando was going to go number
one, but as a former teammate now, and
just kind of knowing how he developed
and got to that point, what was that
like seeing him go number one?
>> Uh, I mean, kind of like you said, we
all knew was coming, but I mean, I was
just very excited for him. I mean, he
really deserves it. Uh, just a real
genuine, hardworking
uh dude and a really good friend. Um,
and I just I'm excited to see what he
has for his career. He's going to be a
great player.
>> Omar, one of the first things Aaron said
was your toughness and your your your
fearlessness. What in your life has
maybe shaped those two traits for you?
>> Uh, I would say um really my
relationship with Christ. Um, that's
kind of what really shaped it. Um,
coming across that my sophomore year. uh
just going through things. That's really
what kind of made me tough and fearless
cuz I know that at the end of the day he
he is the one who has a plan and
everything's going to go according to
it. And so just trusting in him. And
then I would obviously say
uh I'll probably go my parents just they
were both athletes in college and so
they've been through what I've been
where I was at and so just how they
raised me growing up and raised my
sisters and me um was they always made
sure they pushed us uh and never let us
get laxidasical or complacent. So,
>> what were you hearing after your junior
year as far Did you reach out to the
advisory board in the league to find out
what round you might go in and how much
did you help yourself this past year,
you think?
>> Uh, no. I didn't I didn't really have
any uh plans or idea of going uh after
my junior year. Um, so I didn't really
ask. But what really helped me going
into this past year was my just the
conversations I had with my offensive
coordinator.
um he just really told me straight out
what I needed to do or what I could do
to get to this point. Um and so he
really said it was up to me and what I
did. And also I would say my teammate
Elijah Sarah, we all he always pushed me
to be a better player. We pushed each
other and held each other accountable.
Uh and that's kind of what got me here
to this point. Everybody good? Thank you
everyone.
>> Thank you'all.